NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING THE
FILMING OF THIS PRODUCTION
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
What are you waiting for? Take him away!
Know your place.
We caught Osman, your highness.
As you ordered, they are taking him here.
Today is the Day of Titans!
Day of Titans!
Welcome to Hell, Osman.
Are you the Hellhound?
Soon, you will understand whether it is
Hellhound or Azreal.
So be it.
Allah is eternal! Allah is the truth!
Take Osman inside! Hurry up!
Close the gates at once!
With Osman, came three other Turks.
Flatyos is taking care of them, your
highness.
Osman…
Hurry up!
Break down the door!
You shouldn’t come to this castle this
often.
Sometimes I wonder if you’ve become the
victim of your anger.
I will come here frequently until you
empty this castle.
Frequently, huh?
Still hopeful, you are!
Be quick!
Hurry up!
Osman, I don’t know if you’ve noticed but
you are going to do die very soon.
We were taught to live like this, Nikola.
As if we are always going to die soon.
As if you are going to die very soon, huh?
I learned so many thing about Turks.
However, if I combine all of them…
… they would only make a very short book.
A short book is enough for a decent man.
We are told to read!
For this reason, even our arrows have only
a single target.
Our Dhikr is one as well as our object.
This is what makes us invincible!
But you lost, Osman!
Those who think of Death as Shahada never
loses!
Our path is Victory, and our name is
Victor!
But you lost, Osman! You lost!
Did you really think you’d win like this?
Did you really? You lost!
This is it!
Find them!
Don’t let them leave the castle!
Osman is fleeing!
What’s happening? Nikola!
They are fighting inside! Osman must have
broken free!
Nikola!
Break down the gate!
Catch him!
Nikola!
Nikola, are you okay?
Damn it, it won’t open!
I’m going to kill you, Osman!
Don’t leave him alone!
Osman!
It doesn’t work.
You can’t run away forever, Osman!
Let’s go!
Open the gate, Aygül!
Osman!
My Bey!
Aygül!
Get out!
Go!
Come on!
Come on, Osman!
Osman!
We are leaving, brothers!
Let’s go!
We are going to save the prisoners
in exchange of golds.
I will come back. Place a hay cart at the
marked area.
Osman!
One day, these games are going to be over!
We will have a fight against each other!
Lion Hunter Flatyos and Kara Osman!
On that day…
… I promise you that…
… I’m going to eat your heart out!
Open the gate!
Let’s go!
Feudal Landlord Nikola is dying!
How can he die?
Hurry up!
Nikola!
You said Romans would be strong once
again.
You said we’d take our flag to Jerusalem.
Nikola...
Hear me out Nikola!
Hear me.
Who is going to resurrect you now Rome!?
They stabbed our lands just like this
dagger, Nikola.
But I promise you...
...that I will pull them out just like I
pull this dagger.
Nikola?!
Nikola!
Soldier, summon the physician!
Hold on my friend!
Nikola?!
Go!
Allah is eternal!
It’s a trap!
Allah is the truth!
What were you doing there?
Did we kill him?
The dagger didn’t go down deep.
I told you not to come.
I want to unsheathe my sword and die for
our cause.
Catch that one!
It’s me, Osman!
Aygül?
What are you doing here?
I’ve come to help you.
We don’t need your help! Go back at once!
Are you afraid that I will die?
If so, don’t. Because I’m already dead.
I’m a spirit which came to help you.
I won’t leave even if you tell me to.
Aygül, may you do what I tell you to!
Don’t follow me!
I want to help you!
Then, do what I ask you to!
Don’t follow me, Aygül!
The order is yours, my Bey!
Let’s go!
Your eyes killed me, Osman!
What can our enemy do to me?
I grew up waiting for you to come!
You can’t prevent me from dying for
your path!
I told you not to come but you did
anyways.
Yes, It’s true.
Then, why did you come?
Don’t question but see me, Osman.
I’m nothing like old Aygül anymore.
I want to become an Alp.
I want to become a martyr and reach to
heaven.
Göktuğ.
May you build a fire there.
I will stigmatize the wound of uncle’s
daughter.
Come with me, my girl.
My beautiful Bala.
You are sorrowful of not having a child.
But Aygul feels the opposite.
For this reasons, they say ‘the best in
something’.
And Allah tells us to never lose our hope.
With hope, we’ll go on our path.
Do you love Osman Bey so much, Bala?
How much do you love him?
I don’t have to answer this
question, Targun.
However, if you wonder this much…
… I threw everything from my heart and
filled it with his love.
If I loved a man this much, I’d rip out
everything from his heart besides myself.
My Bala, do you think Osman vanquished
that dog already?
The medallion and the map saved your
life, Nikola.
Nikola, the new ruler of the new Rome.
You want to become the emperor, huh?
He did it, Flatyos.
He entered the castle...
... overcame the trap...
…and killed me.
Your dreams saved you, Nikola.
The dreams of becoming the new Emperor.
This is a sign.
I am reborn, Flatyos.
Just like Mithra who killed the black ox.
Reborn, like the god of kings, Dionysus.
Or, like Jesus Christ.
I promise you that...
... I’ll make them all pay for this.
I’m going to wander around the Tents
of Kayıs, and impale them all.
At the end, I’ll make a forest made out o
f impales.
Then, I’ll place the head of Osman at the
top of those impales.
Aygül!
Let me do it, Aygül!
It’s brand iron! What do you think you
are doing?
It’s brand and it hurts, uncle’s daughter.
What’s the thing that hurts you more than
this brand iron, Aygül?
Tell me what it is.
I have a baby, Osman.
What baby?
A baby, Osman.
From Alişar.
From the man who you beheaded.
Choose your words wisely, Aygül.
What Alişar?
Every life given is from Allah.
I have a nephew now, huh?
Is it a boy?
Tell me. Is it a boy?
What’s his name?
He doesn’t have one.
Doesn’t have a name?
Then, his uncle will name him!
May his name be Kayıalp.
May he be an Alp for Kayı.
So, we have a new alp, my Bey.
With Allah’s permission, he will be a
warrior like Aygül Hatun.
Well said.
What’s the meaning of this, Hazal?
Dündar Bey. Do you want me to use this
sword?
Against whom, you would use that sword?
Against your daughter!
What are you saying, Hatun? How will you
use that sword against my daughter?
Like this! Just like she used it against
me!
Where is Aygül?
She was already at the Tent and Selcan
Hatun was hiding her from everyone!
She set her against me as if she is an
Alp!
She nearly killed me!
Now I’m asking you, Dündar Bey!
Am I to wait for the next time she is
going to attack me?
Or am I to attack her with my sword?
Where’s my daughter?
Where?
May I enter, Dündar Bey?
Come, Selcan Hatun.
I'll come back later.
Wait, Selcan Hatun.
Whose baby is that?
Your daughter's.
Aygül's.
You...
What are you saying?
Aygül's?
How?
From the man who was beheaded
by Osman. From Alişar.
Alişar?
Alişar...
Why did you hide...
...this baby from me...
...all this time?
Why?
How can this man return alive?
Aygül.
My daughter...
Your father is curious about where
you were, Aygül!
We were at Kulucahisar, in the
lair of the enemy.
We stabbed Nikola in the heart
and we left safe in sound.
What did you do?
What is it, brother? You look sad?
Osman!
Don't worry. It wasn't right on his heart.
He might be alive.
Run to tell him to get well soon.
Leave aside not listening to us,
you are going over your limit now!
You are acting rebellious.
I'm not doing it to be rebellious. I went there
to show them we won't leave them in peace.
If you weren't my brother...
Everything would be so easy,
wouldn't it, brother?
But I'm your brother.
Even if you don't want it,
I'll serve the Kayıs.
I'll raid enemy castles every day.
Even if you don't want it,
I'll fight every day.
Until our tents live in prosperity and
know its enemies well.
-Nikola.
-My dear friend.
Come to yourselves. Victory is still ours.
We conquered Kulucahisar.
They...
...only saved their captives.
What did we do?
We stabbed the Kayı tents...
They? They stabbed me.
Don't you ever forget that...
...great states win wars.
Wars.
Little ones consolidate themselves with
heroism. I don't like consolations.
We will be on our way. Whatever the Kayıs
took from us...
...we'll take them back one by one.
They will come and attack us.
They will come and wound us.
Who told you that it will be easy? Who?
My dear friend, are there
any easy victories?
-There is no easy victory, Nikola.
-There is no easy victory.
Whenever you see someone successful,
know that they have been through pain.
Then, what will we do?
We will ask for the pain.
Then? We'll recreate Rome.
We'll be at Söğüt tomorrow.
We'll burn it, crush it.
We'll prepare it to get occupied again.
Let them enjoy their little heroism.
We won't leave them a place to live,
land to stand, breath to take.
Today, I have reborn.
Like Mithras who killed the black bull. Like
the god of the kings, Dionysus, I've reborn.
Who can kill someone who reborn?
Who can beat someone who reborn?
I'm immortal now! Immortal!
Long live, Nikola! Long live, Nikola!
With the name of Allah.
O' people!
The Kayı Tribe has a new Alp!
His name is Kayı Alp.
His grandfather is, Dündar Bey,
Süleyman Shah's son.
His mother is a Ghazi of Kulucahisar,
Aygül Hatun.
He will be raised as a Kayı, and become an
honorable member of our tribe.
My good-hearted boy.
You are the pride of this tribe.
Aygül Hatun, come on.
Dismount your horse and hug your father
who waits for you in longing.
My daughter... Aygül...
My daughter...
My girl, you are wounded.
It's the holy war. That can happen.
Why do you hide, my girl?
You aren't the one who should be ashamed.
It's me.
Me.
Oh, my Aygül. Why did you hide my
grandchild from me? Why?
Bala. Let's go. Whoever is happy about
my arrival can come.
As you wish, my bey.
This is my birthday.
Today, I've reborn.
Who wants to give me a beautiful gift?
We! We!
Who?
Who wants to burn Söğüt?
We! We!
Who wants to pierce the heart of the Kayıs?
The command is yours, Flatyos.
Take the cruelest men with you...
...and in any way, turn Söğüt
into a hell...
...and make Osman's heart burn in it.
Söğüt is your duty, Flatyos.
And this is mine.
When the time comes,
I'll pierce Osman's heart with this.
Then, I'll reborn again, again and again.
Look, what my ancestor Farabi says...
...a city is built around virtue and
contains neighborhood relations.
Either they are under stone walls
or tents make no difference.
Can a tribe built with tents, be a city?
Why can't it? As long as minds are united.
Why would building stone walls
be civilization?
Civilization is the thing that is
left after a calamity.
What is left after a great calamity,
Savcı?
Respect, love, mercy, honor, and faith.
So, everything, Lena. Everything.
Turkism is a great tree.
Oghuz is the biggest branch of that tree.
And Kayı is the greenest leave of
that branch.
We are reaching for the fruit, Lena.
Where am I in your heart, Osman?
Is there any care left for me after
the love of the state and people?
Bala, the heart is an armageddon flower.
Love is its leaves reaching to Allah.
And you are my garden.
Bala... You are my light. The fire of
your eyes illuminates the dark.
Your smile removes all sadness, Bala.
Are you jealous of the state and people?
If there are no lovers, no love...
What good they can do?
We were exiled from our home in a dawn...
Wherever we go, we aren't local.
We have sorrow from dark nights...
We only have a baton, a bag and Allah.
We only have Allah... Only Allah.
Sorrow from every breath,
it's all yours...
Without you, there would be no love.
Who is this man?
Looks like a miserable man.
Lord Nikola changed a lot.
He has reborn.
I hope you are as wild as they say,
Cerkutay.
Because we'll do horrible things with you.
What's horrible to you is cute
to us, Flatyos.
We'll see, Cerkutay.
When I reached Kulucahisar, the heathen
were expecting me.
There is a traitor in the tribe. They
found it out and sent a word.
I'm suspicious of Targon Hatun.
Bala.
Keep your eye on her. Follow her every step.
As you say, my bey. But are you sure?
I don't have evidence. But if you
bring evidence, I'll end it.
As you say, don't worry.
Thank you. Thank you.
Aunt, you sound her out.
-My bey, may I enter?
-Come, Boran.
My bey, we have news from Kumral Abdal.
Flatyos is going to Söğüt with his men.
To Söğüt?
Inform Bamsı Bey. We should meet
at the alp tent at once.
Tell me, Boran.
My bey, Yavlak Arslan is in
Dündar Bey's tent.
Osman, don't go there.
You'll fight each other.
It will be that way. But I have no
chance. They are after something.
I should know what's their aim,
what they are after.
Osman, when will the peace come?
I'm struggling for the peace of
our children, Bala.
Our destiny is a struggle. Whatever
happens today, be strong.
For our children.
Children...
He entered Kulucahisar, huh?
And he severely wounded Nikola?
How many times will you ruin my plan?
What plan are you talking about,
Yavlak Arslan?
You said that you separated your way,
Osman. Why are you here now?
You don't like the ones sitting.
Are you here to sit now?
If you are going to plan without me,
you shouldn't come to this tribe.
You entered the castle, Osman.
You wounded Nikola on his heart.
He wanted that.
You took him down but couldn't kill him.
He was destined to live, then.
But now he knows. That castle isn't his.
I can behead them at any time.
Despite that, he offered peace.
Peace?
It would be better if that dog was dead.
We'd get what we want.
But this matter will be on the table
during the peace talk.
What peace? What talk?
Osman. I need this peace. My aim isn't
becoming Nikola's brother.
It's catching him off-guard.
Nikola, who was raided in his castle,
whose men died...
...instead of going mad,
he is talking about peace?
Why would someone with that power
want to make peace?
Take the barrel to Söğüt.
Flatyos knows what to do with them.
Osman... Let's see what he will do
when he hears that Söğüt is afire.
Let him run after little heroisms.
I'll march to my real target.
We all know that Nikola needs time. You
should know that we need that time as well.
You don't have a single moment to wait.
Would you believe me that they
are preparing to strike us?
Where do you get those news now, Osman?
It's not important where I get them.
You should listen to what I say.
It's enough now, Osman. You intervened
my meeting that day.
For the favor of your father,
uncle, and brothers...
...I didn't say a thing.
But, if you get into my way again...
If you do something to stop the peace...
Speak, dog! Speak!
Tell me what you will do?
You think that they are deceiving us with
peace and we are believing like little children!
No! Not like that! While we speak of the
peace, they won't attack Söğüt.
While your uncle and speak
of the peace, I'll attack İnegöl.
You are making plans, huh?
Yes, I came here to say that.
This is a dangerous game, Yavlak Arslan.
You ask me and my uncle to go to the castle
of a man who is wounded in his heart.
And also, you are planning something else.
Don't worry, Savcı Bey.
Nikola can't risk facing me.
He knows well that I'll destroy Kulucahisar
if he does something to you.
You are all wrong. Today's business is Söğüt.
Kulucahisa is tomorrow. İnegöl is for the future.
If I take İnegöl, can Nikola stay
in Kulucahisar, Osman?
You can't take İnegöl.
Only my brother and uncle will get hurt.
Even when you are trying to protect, you
are going over your level, Osman.
As you got into Kulucahisar and left,
like a wolf getting into a herd...
...we can be lions when needed,
hit the gazelles, and leave.
All right, brother. All right.
I have no doubt about that.
But the dagger of the enemy
is pointing at Söğüt.
I'm going to go to Söğüt. Yavlak can go
to İnegöl if he wants to.
And you can run into the traps of Nikola.
But know this, when Nikola's soldiers
ambush you, it's enough for you to...
...roar once. Your brother will
come and rescue you again.
The heathen enemy is completely
out of control.
There are dark clouds near Söğüt.
It seems that they want payback for
the dagger that pierced Nikola.
They think that Kulucahisar's worth
is a little dagger wound.
We aren't finished yet for them
to come for payback.
My heart isn't cold yet.
I promise to the soul of
my ancestor, Oghuz Khagan...
...that my heart is isn't cold yet.
Brothers, the day for a siege
on Kulucahisar is soon.
Today, we'll kick the enemy our of Söğüt.
Tomorrow, maybe closer than tomorrow...
We'll take Kulucahisar, which belongs to
our Ghazis and martyrs.
Allahu Akbar!
For the Ghazis who say ''Allah Allah!''
For the faithful martyrs!
For the commander of Ghazis,
Süleiman Shah!
Allahu Akbar!
For Ertuğrul Ghazi, the valiant sultan,
who is expecting our victory!
Allahu Akbar! Allahu Akbar!
Don't worry. Nothing will go wrong.
We expect your victory in İnegöl.
From now, we will put all our
benevolence to Kulucahisar.
Of course, Dündar Bey.
Don't doubt that.
-Our tribe and father are under your protection.
-Don't worry, brother. You can go.
Thank you.
My bey.
-Abdurrahman Ghazi?
-Yes, my bey.
What's happening in the tribe?
Dündar, Savcı and Gündüz are
talking to Yavlak Arslan.
-Yavlak Arslan?
-Right, my bey.
-What about Osman?
-My bey...
...Osman Bey is with his alps. Before the
battle, they shouted your name.
So, he is going for
a holy war again.
So, he is shouting my name...
Osman Bey is just like you, my bey.
Just like your youth, my bey.
May Osman live long.
May he become a bey...
...and his name gets shouted.
Amin, my bey.
Amin.
-More power to your elbow.
-Thank you.
-Was she always like this?
-She wasn't.
She had been married to a man she didn't
love. And she turned into this.
Did Selcan Hatun turn her into this?
Isn't Selcan Hatun the most
powerful woman of these tents?
Because of her age, everyone
respects her. But...
...this is more about the mind
than the age.
Mashallah, my girls. What
were you talking about here?
We were talking about Aygül Hatun.
We are sad about her condition.
-What's wrong with Aygül?
-She is a valiant warrior. A pride.
Yes, she is. So are you. You are a bey's
daughter. We heard about his valor.
And how they took his life, too.
-Why did those heathens take you captive?
-I come after my father, Selcan Hatun.
They knew what would happen
to them, if they hadn't taken me captive.
Right, right...
But if you are such an important woman....
...why don't your kin nor Nikola are
looking for you? Targon, what is this?
Tell me.
-Selcan Hatun.
-Yes.
-Aygül is in Dündar Bey's tent.
-So?
Hazal Hatun just entered the tent.
Did you put your eyes on the
Bey's place, Aygül?
I put my eyes on you, Hazal.
I put my eyes on my mother's killer.
Don't you remember that your mother
attempted to kill all Kayı Beys and women?
I had a score to settle with you.
I remember that.
Where did you find that sword, Lena?
It looks good on your hand.
If there is a lunatic in the tribe who
is wandering with a sword...
...you should take a measure, Aygül.
What good can you do even if you
had measures from up and down, Lena?
Be careful, Aygül.
I'm not your step mother.
I have no pity.
Come on, hurry.
I need to catch with my uncle.
Savcı Bey!
There are sounds coming from Dündar Bey's
tent. Lena Hatun and Aygül Hatun are fighting.
What?
Take this, Rum girl!
Come, then, Alişar's wife!
Aygül!
-Aygül...
-Don't move, Savcı bey!
Aren't you an alp of Osman bey?
What are you doing here while your
bey is on a campaign?
So, Osman bey went to Söğüt?
I have no quarrel with you, Savcı Bey.
But this isn't the end of it.
-Are you all right?
-Savcı bey!
If this woman doesn't leave the tents,
either I, Hazal Hatun or she will die!
Hold there. What's in them?
-It's from Gemlik. Olive oil.
-Give me.
Here.
-It's fine, go on.
-Thank you.
Here we go, Cerkutay.
Everyone to their positions.
-So, we separate here?
-True, Bamsı Bey.
When we find out the goal of the
weasels, we'll let each other know.
-Once we find out theirs, ours will be decided.
-All right, my lion. All right.
-Godspeed!
-Thank you. May Allah bless our efforts.
Come on!
We are the warriors of Kayı!
Our intentions are for Allah's approval.
We came to these lands to spread
the religion of Allah, the true faith!
Thank Allah for protecting us against
tyrants, who puts faith in our hearts!
Forever, for justice!
Forever, for freedom! Allahu Akbar!
We don't want you here! Get out!
Leave here! We don't want you!
You filthy barbarians! Get out!
Nobody wants you here, you barbarians!
Osman bey is on his way to Söğüt.
-Attack me!
-Attack you?
I told you to do it!
Targon Hatun, what's going on here?
I'm talking to you, Targon! What are
you doing here? Who is this man?
'Osman left the tents. He is on his way
to Söğüt' What does that mean?
It means that there is a traitor in the
tents. Someone is leaking information.
-What were you doing here?
-I'm not used to sitting, Bala Hatun.
I wanted to take a walk. Then, I saw
this man. I realized he was after something.
Don't get far again without telling
anyone. You are under our protection.
As it's known, one who leaves the tents
becomes prey for the wolves.
Let's go back to the tribe.
Come on.
What does that mean, Nicola?
This means the castle has been civilized.
Savcı Bey, should I have brought rugs,
carpets or sheepskin?
Stop talking no sense about civilization!
- We don't appreciate this insult!
- Get off your throne, talk face to face.
I was hoping that we'd make peace.
You can't make peace like that.
Hah, this is so a Turkish Bey move.
What do you think Turks Beys are, Nicola?
Ha?
We have made thousands of wars
and peace with...
those Chinese Emperors who you couldn't
even imagine in your dreams...
and those Caesers who you are proud of.
I love Turks, Savcı Bey.
I really do.
You claim all the great empires
in history. That's cool.
Beys. Kayı Beys.
You are talking to Rome Governor.
Kayı Beys, ha?
Kayı Beys.
Do you know the story of Oghuzs, Nicola?
I like history, Dündar Bey.
I know but...
You should remember that all the history
was written in Rome.
You live like moles in nooks.
You capture women, olds an kids.
And you call it your history.
Turkish is spoken from Chinese to Rome
borders.
Do you know why Nicola?
Because our ancestors conquered there.
We even conquered this castle you are
living in, Nicola.
Do you want it back?
Do you want war?
Do you want war?!
We need fire.
Turks are friendly.
They will give me.
Firstly, you'll accept that Kulucahisar...
is under my command.
Secondly, you are going to swear on...
your dignity and honor that you
are not going to attack Kulucahisar.
What?
How else can I be sure?
This agreement won't work.
Savcı Bey, there would not be an agreement
without this article.
What's the point of making an agreement...
if you are going to attack here anytime
you want?
And...
Osman...
he is not going to come here again.
Neither in daylight nor in night.
Neither through the door nor
through the gates.
Do you understand me?
What's it? Are you worried about the
fact that you can't hold Osman down?
- It's our concern, Nicola.
- No, that's not true.
This is all Rome's and Turks' concern,
Savcı Bey.
Osman is a rebel.
Look here, Rome Governor!
Watch your mouth about my brother.
Even in front of me, how you dare!
Okay.
I didn't know you loved Osman that much.
Let's cut it short.
This article must be added
to the agreement.
If Rome attack any property of Turks...
this agreement will be broken.
Turkish property?
What does this mean?
This is a broad term.
What is this, Nicola?!
Hi, blacksmith.
Tell me.
I need fire.
Do you, really?
Osman!
Sogut is my town!
You have to ask my permission
before visiting here.
I am just like you, showing up
without permission, Osman.
You are a guest.
The first move is yours, then.
Sure.
Have a nice day.
Hey! What are you doing with that
barrel? You ruined the ground!
I'll clean it with fire.
Hey! Where are you going?
Give the candle back to me!
I'm talking to you!
Bring the candle back!
I told you I'd clean up.
I missed you, Bamsı.
You took me and left in the castle
last time, Osman.
So, who is going to save your
capture brother and uncle?
Dogs!
I left the castle with you, I saved
my men.
Now I'll arrive at the castle with you,
and save my brother and uncle.
- My Bey, my Bey!
- Do it!
No!
Osman Bey.
You can lean on me from now on.
Thank you, my valiant.
- Tell me your name.
- My name is Gence Bey.
Nice.
Just like that.
You are looking far better now!
We just need some... yeah
now it is fantastic.
It's absolutely fantastic!
You ignoble dog!
You are going to pay!
You are going to pay for this!
Here we are.
It's excellent!
I asked Osman.
"How are you going to get out of here?"
Do you wonder his respond?
"I am going to leave like a wolf
that leaves from a sheepfold."
Hold on, uncle!
We... we... we are going to kill you!
- Dündar Bey, he did what he said.
- I'll kill you.
- Dündar Bey, you are so handsome now.
- I'll kill you!
I'll murder you!
Hold on, uncle, hold on.
Dündar Bey, believe me.
It's going to be okay.
You ignoble dog!
You are going to pay.
You are going... to... pay
Hold on, uncle!
Hold on!
Uncle... uncle!
Hello! I am the new uncle!
Hahaha!
You look fantastic!
Give me a minute, here, here...
Hold on for a second!
Yeah here it is!
I need to squish it a little bit.
Yes, it's getting better.
Let's press here too.
Beautiful
And here is some more just for you!
I love sculpturing!
Believe me, you look better now
Yes.
- I should leave, Osman Bey.
- Be my guest, come to my tent.
You are too busy.
- I'll come someday.
- Eyvallah(thank you) I look forward for it.
He says my uncle and my brother
are in Kulucahisar.
Where is Bamsı Bey?
My Osman, my Osman.
Check this out.
- Look.
- Masha Allah(praise be!)
Look who I run across with on my way here.
Cerkutay.
Bamsı Bey.
We are done with Sogut.
Why, son?
It's Nicola again, isn't it?
Yes, actually.
- Son, what are you going to do?
- I'll go to Kulucahisar.
What's it, Vladius?
Are you bored of me?
Ha?
I told you.
I'll visit that castle more often.
Until you leave there!
You are wrong! We need to deal with
Sogut first, then Kulucahisar, then Inegol.
What if I conquer Inegol? Can Nicola
manage Kulucahisar then?
You can't take Inegol.
My uncle and my brother will be victims!
You are crossing the respect
line, Osman!
You can leave Kulucahisar like a wolf
leaving from a sheepfold, but I am the lion.
I kill the whole gazelle herd.
I'll go to Sogut. Yavlak can go
to Inegol.
And Nicola will entrap you!
Osman, Osman is right again.
He tricked us, ignoble.
That dog planned this all.
But it's not going to be that easy, uncle.
I am going to kill him before he kills me.
We don't fear anyone, son.
Talking about how glorious Turks are all
the time...
Dear Kayı Beys. Do you know what
I should do now?
I should wait for you to hear the
news from Sogut being destroyed.
But I won't be able to wait, I guess.
Father.
- Gündüz.
- Father.
Son.
I have a bad feeling, Abdurrahman Ghazi.
Our men are returning!
Vladius is wounded!
He is wounded!
Open the gates!
Gates!
When Nicola entraps you,
just scream for help.
I will save you no matter what!
Vladius, vladius, my saint friend!
Vladius, Vladius!
Vladius! my saint friend!
Vladius!
He is alive!
He is still alive!
Osman Bey!
Command your soldiers to stop!
If I throw this torch to the barrel,
we all are going to blow up!
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
Nicola!
Nicola.
Osman.
Release my uncle and brother!
Set them free!
This cruel has two options. Kneeling to
Turks, or kneeling to Turks.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com